In this video, we're going to work the problem of finding
在这段视频中，我们将探讨如何
the closest point out of a set of points to some other given point.
从一组点中找到最接近其他给定点的点。
We'll start by doing an instance of this problem by ourselves.
首先，我们将自己举一个这个问题的实例。
To do that, I've begun by drawing
为此，我首先绘制
a Cartesian coordinate grid and choosing a set S of points,
笛卡尔坐标网格，然后选择一组 S 点
which you can see here,
，你可以在这里看到
another point P, which is one, negative one.
另一个点 P，也就是一个，负点。
We're going to find the point in S that is closest to
我们要在 S 中找到最接近
P. The first thing I'm going to do is to draw my points on my Cartesian plane.
P 的点。我要做的第一件事就是在笛卡尔平面上画出我的点。
Now, I can begin working through this.
现在，我可以开始解决这个问题了。
First, I need some domain knowledge.
首先，我需要一些领域知识。
I need the mathematical definition of the distance between two points,
我需要两点之间距离的数学定义
which if you don't remember,
，如果你不记得的话，那就
is the difference in the x values squared plus the difference in
是 x 值的平方之差加上
the y values squared and then we take the square root of that.
y 值的平方差，然后我们取其平方根。
So the way that I would do this is calculate the distance between P and two,
所以我这样做的方法是计算 P 和 2、
seven, and I would come up with 8.06.
7 之间的距离，然后我会得出 8.06。
Then, I would compute the distance between P and 10,
然后，我会计算 P 和 10、
5 and come up with 10.82.
5 之间的距离，然后得出 10.82。
The first point was closer,
第一点离得更近了，
so I'm going to keep that.
所以我会保留的。
This point is 7.07 away,
距离这个点还有 7.07，
so I'm going to keep the new closest point so far.
所以我将保留到目前为止最近的新点。
This point is 7.81 away,
距离这个点
so eight, negative two is still closer.
还有7.81的距离，所以八点，负二更接近。
This point is 5.66 away,
这个点距离为 5.66，
so we have a new closest point.
所以我们有了新的最近点。
This point is 9.06 away,
距离这个点是 9.06，
so negative three, negative five is closer.
所以负三、负五更接近。
This point is 9.22 away,
距离这个点还有9.22，
so negative three, negative five is still closer.
所以负三、负五还更接近。
And there are no more points to test, so negative three,
而且没有其他要测试的分数了，所以
negative five is my answer to which point is closest to one, negative one.
我的答案是负三，负五是最接近一的点，阴性的。
If we visually inspect this picture,
如果我们目视这张照片，
that seems pretty reasonable.
这似乎很合理。
It looks like the closest.
它看起来像是最接近的。
Now, I write down exactly what I just did.
现在，我准确地写下了我刚才所做的事情。
I computed one squared plus eight squared,
我计算了一平方加八平方，
took the square root and got about 8.06.
取平方根得到大约 8.06。
I computed the square root of nine squared plus six squared and got 10.82,
我计算了九平方加上六平方的平方根，得到了 10.82，
and I compared 10.82 to 8.06 and said 8.06 is smaller.
我将 10.82 与 8.06 进行了比较，说8.06更小。
I computed the square root of seven squared plus negative one squared and got 7.07,
我计算了七平方加负一平方的平方根得到7.07，然后
and I compared 7.07 to 8.06 and said 7.07 is smaller,
我比较了7.07和8.06并说7.07更小，
so this is a better choice.
所以这是一个更好的选择。
Then I compared the square root of six squared plus negative five squared and got 7.81.
然后我比较了六平方加上负五平方的平方根，得到了 7.81。
I compared 7.81 with 7.07 and got that 7.07 was smaller and so on and so on and so on.
我将 7.81 与 7.07 进行了比较，得知 7.07 更小，依此类推，依此类推。
And then when I got to the end,
然后当我走到最后时，
I gave my answer as negative three, negative five.
我给出的答案是负三，负五。
These seem like reasonable steps,
这些步骤似乎是合理的，
but we actually glossed over
但实际上我们掩盖
something that we did in the process of writing these steps down.
了在编写这些步骤的过程中所做的事情。
carefully because if we're missing steps,
仔细地写下我们的步骤非常重要，因为如果我们
we're going to miss them when we go to generalize and end up having a problem.
错过了步骤，那么当我们进行概括并最终遇到问题时，我们就会错过它们。
Here's an important clue.
这是一条重要的线索。
Look at this step where we give an answer of negative three, negative five.
看看这个步骤，我们给出的答案是负三，负五。
When we go to generalize,
当我们概括时，
we're going to ask, "Why did we use negative three, negative five?"
我们会问：“为什么我们使用负三，负五？”
Then we're going to notice we don't see negative three,
然后我们会注意到我们在
negative five anywhere else.
其他任何地方都看不到负三、负五。
The fact that our answer seemingly comes out of
我们的答案似乎
nowhere indicates that we're missing something.
突然出现，这一事实表明我们遗漏了一些东西。
We did some step without consciously thinking about it and writing it down,
我们在没有意识地思考和写下来的情况下做了一些步骤，
and we need to fix that before we go on.
我们需要在继续之前修复这个问题。
We may notice this now,
我们现在可能会注意到这一点，当
we may notice it when we go to generalize,
我们进行概括时，我们可能会注意到这一点
in which case we need to come back and fix it.
，在这种情况下，我们需要回来修复它。
Why was it that we picked negative three,
为什么我们
negative five as our answer here?
在这里选择负三、负五作为答案？
Reviewing our last steps,
回顾我们最后
the last remaining dotted line of length 5.66 is what we were keeping track of,
的步骤，最后剩下的长度为5.66的虚线是我们一直在跟踪的，也是我们
our best choice so far.
迄今为止的最佳选择。
We started at point two, seven,
我们从第二、七点开始，
then we went around and updated it each time we found a shorter distance.
然后我们四处走动，每次找到更短的距离时都会对其进行更新。
However, as we wrote our steps,
但是，在我们编写步骤时，
we never mentioned the point that went with the shortest distance so far.
我们从未提及迄今为止距离最短的点。
We should go back and fix our steps to include that.
我们应该回过头来修复我们的步骤以将其包括在内。
We start with a best choice of two, seven.
我们从二、七的最佳选择开始。
When we got to eight, negative two and decided 7.07 was smaller,
当我们达到八，负二并决定7.07小一点时，
we updated our closest point to eight, negative two.
我们将最接近的点更新为八，负二。
When we got to negative three,
当我们达到负三，
negative five and found that 5.66 was smaller,
负五并发现5.66更小时，
we updated our best choice to negative three, negative five.
我们将最佳选择更新为负三，负五。
Now, this answer at the end makes sense.
现在，最后的这个答案是有道理的。
It is whatever our best choice was last.
这是我们最后的最佳选择。
Now we're ready to generalize,
现在我们已经准备好进行概括了
which we'll do in the next video.
，我们将在下一个视频中这样做。